모든 경찰에게 알린다
모든 반경으로
All units...
quadrant search in progress
현재 5명의 탈출범들을 수색하라
for five escaped convicts
currently at large.
맥아더 길에 있는 모든 경찰차들은
Units at MacArthur Causeway,
stand by
즉각 동서 방향을 봉쇄하라
for immediate East
and West shutdown.
헬기는 채널11로 보고하라
Air fleet reporting to base
command on channel 11.
렉싱톤 센터에서 수상한 움직임이 보고되었다
Suspicious activity reported
at Lexington Center.
마이애미-웨스트 교도소에서 탈출한 죄수들은
Escaped convicts
from Miami-West Prison
아직 우리구역안에 있어
running loose
in our very own neighborhood.
이곳을 뜨는 모든 수단을
조사해야겠네요
All looking for the
fastest ticket out of town.
그러니까 이놈들이군요
So these are the bad boys, huh?
맞아 그리고
Yeah, and then some.
교도소에서 브로워드 카운티까지 가는
We got bikes, boots, air units
오토바이 헬기 등을 찾아놨어
from the prison
to Broward County.
이봐 마리노, 이 사진 사본
최대한빨리 복사해줘
Hey, Marino, I need copies
of these photos ASAP, thanks.
Bay지점으로 가는 지상경찰 두그룹은
Ground units Bravo and
Charlie en route from Bay Point.
응답바랍니다
Please confirm.
여러분
Gentlemen.
반장님
Lieutenant.
시민여러분,
늦어져서 죄송합니다
Ladies and gentlemen,
I am very sorry for the delay.
몇분만 양해 바랍니다
We will have you on your way
in just a few minutes.
감사하고 죄송합니다
Thank you.
Sorry, folks.
안녕하세요
Morning.
좋은아침이죠
이봐 자네
Okay, my friend,
이 버스를 내리는 두가지 방법이있어
there are two ways
off this bus...
조용하고 천천히 내리거나
slowly and quietly
총에 맞아 죽거나
or feet first.
니가 결정해
You decide.
연쇄강간범, 텍스 길로이는 잡았으니까
Tex Gilroy, serial rapist,
in custody.
이제 한놈 잡았군
One down.
그가 말라노크와 아직 접촉 안했나? 프랭크
Has he contacted
the Mala Noche yet, Frank?
아직 안했어
No contact with the current
leaders; we're trying to...
잠깐만
저거 메모 피에로 맞지?
Wait a minute.
That's Memmo Fierro, right?
응
Yeah.
호라시오 반장님 아내를
죽인놈이야
He murdered Marisol...
Horatio's wife,
데코 누나였던...
Delko's sister.
감옥 패거리들과 관련 당국을 조사했는데요
I checked with Prison Gangs,
Organized Crime, ATF.
모두 입을 다물고 있어요
All negative
for planned activity.
꼭 잡을거에요, 반장님
We'll get him, H.
우리가 해야 할 마지막 일이네
If it's the last thing we do.
푸는법 알려줘야되나요?ㅋ
You need a service manual?
묶여있는건 매듭공부하는 해군들도
It's hard to be spontaneous
when you're strapped
풀기 힘들다고
inside of a midshipman's hitch.
알겠어요 ㅋ
You're all thumbs.
무슨 소리지?
What was that?
우아한 여행중이신가?
Traveling in style, eh?
내 보트에서 내려
Get off my boat.
아니 좀 둘러보고싶은데
Nah, I'd rather take
a look around.
보자
Let's see.
해적이라도 만나면 쓰려고 했던
물건인가?
A little something to protect
yourself from pirates?
니가 먼저 이걸 찾고
I bet you wish
싶어한것 같은데
you got to this first.
그러는게 더 좋았을텐데말야
It works a lot better that way.
오 장전도 되있네
Oh, loaded, too.
오늘 난 참 운이 좋구만
My lucky day,
넌 아니고
not yours.
이런~
Damn.
드레스와 보석들이라
Dresses, jewelry.
여자는 어딨어?
Where's the missus?
여자는 있다가 여기서
만나기로 했어
She's meeting me here later.
생각해봐
Think about it, buddy.
여기서 얼마나 멀리갈수 있을것 같아?
How far do you think
you're going to get out here?
왜
Why?
날 걱정해주는거냐?
You doubting me, buddy?
밖으로 나가자구
Let's take it outside.
와우하는 물동이에게 바친다
배포자유, 수정요청을 CSI갤로
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
도망친 보트는 보스톤웨일러고,
The getaway boat
is a Boston Whaler
버지니아의 관문으로 향하고있다
heading for Virginia Key.
반장님, 배들이 비어있어요
Lieutenant,
the additional units out there
그놈이 아마 따돌릴려고 보트를
버렸을거야
are coming up empty.
He may have ditched the boat,
그러니까 항구 수색하고,
그놈 찾아서 데려오게, 울프
so check with the port
and get back to me. Mr. Wolfe?
저 남자는 500파운드 닻에 묶여서
바다아래로 떨어졌어요
The guy rode a 500-pound
anchor to the bottom.
갑판위에서 여러개의
발자국을 찾았어요
Found dozens of prison-issue
treads all over the deck.
이게 메모 피에로 방식이지
This has Memmo Fierro
written all over it.
네
우리가 그놈을 빨리잡지 못하면,
Yeah.
If we don't find him quick,
누군가가 또 죽을거야
he's going to kill again.
그가 원한게 보석이었어요?
All he wanted was jewelry?
더기가 제 보석때문에 죽은건가요?
Dougie's gone over jewelry?
저는 그냥
I just...
저는 그냥 여행할 때 예쁜 장신구가 있으면
I just thought
it was something nice
더 근사할거라고 생각했어요
to bring on the trip.
이딴거 필요없어요
I don't want it.
이봐요 데이지양, 이게 얼마나
힘든일인지 알아요
Look, Daisy, I know
that this is so hard,
하지만 스스로를 탓할 필요 없어요
but you cannot blame yourself.
이 남자였나요?
Is this the man that you saw?
우리 총도 가져갔어요
He took our gun, too,
더기가
the one Doug insisted
총을 가져가자고 그랬어요
we have on the boat.
저는 그 놈이 총을
I could see it
손에 들고 있는것을 봤어요
in his hand.
그 범인은 그 상황을
What he was doing...
즐기는것처럼 보였어요
it's like he took joy in it.
라이언
Ryan,
탈출한 보트 찾았단 이야기 들었어?
did you hear that they
found the getaway boat?
응 그 놈이 도버만에 버렸다며
Yeah, Memmo beached it
at Dover Bay,
이제 우린 그 놈이 어디로 갔는지 몰라
so now we have no idea
how he's getting around.
그가 아마 이 곳으로 가고 있는거라면
Well, he might not
need transportation
더이상 교통수단을 필요없을거야
if he ends up heading
to this location.
황금태양세탁소
Golden Sun Dry Cleaners.
그곳이 그 놈 여자친구가
일하는 곳이야
That's where
his girlfriend works,
그리고 보트를 버린곳에서
1마일도 안되는 거리기도 하고
and it's less than a mile
from where he ditched the boat.
좋아, 캘리가 그쪽에 있어 여자친구 찾을수 있는지 알아볼게
Okay, Calleigh's at the bay;
I'll see if you can find her.
우리를 도와줄 사람이겠지, 안그래?
Guess there's somebody
for everyone, huh?
맞아
Yeah.
Memmo는 지금 5년째 마이애미 교도소에 있었잖아요
Memmo's been in Miami-West
Prison for five years now?
탈옥했어요 7명의 죄수들과 함께 말이죠
He escaped, along
with seven other people.
뭐라구요?
What?
머야, 지금 여기서 탈옥얘기 처음 들은거예요?
What, is this the first
you're hearing of this?
네, 저는 바빠요
Yes, I work.
세탁소에서 하루종일 일하거든요
I'm at the dry
cleaners 24-7.
아무것도 몰라요
I had no idea.
그러니까 그 사람은
당신과 연락한적이 없나요?
So he has not tried
to contact you?
없어요
No.
내가 아는한 없었네요
Not that I know of.
에르난데스씨, 핸드폰 있으세요?
Do you have a cell phone,
Ms. Hernandez?
우리를 위해 휴대폰 좀
Would you check it
휴대폰 좀 확인해 볼래요?
for us, please?
부재중 전화는 하나도 없어요
No missed calls from anyone.
그 귀걸이들은 어디서 났죠?
Where'd you get those earrings?
선물받은거예요
/ 누구한테요?
They were a gift.
From who?
Memmo한테? /아니요, 말했잖아요
그를 본 적도 없어요
From Memmo? No. I told you.
I have not seen him.
진짜요? 저한테 그 귀걸이와 세트인
목걸이가 있거든요
Really? Because I have the
matching necklace, and I got it
오늘 아침 Memmo가 강도질한 여성에게서
얻은거예요
off a woman who was robbed on
her boat this morning by Memmo.
알아요? 그 놈은 벌써 탈출하고
한 사람을 죽였어요
You know, he's killed
one man since his escape.
그러니까 우리랑 장난
So stop playing games
그만하시죠 이본씨
with us, Ivonne.
밖에서 그와 만났었어요
He met me out back...
세탁소 뒤에서 한시간 전에요
behind the dry cleaners,
about an hour ago.
받아 받으라고!
Take it. Take it!
이게 머야? 귀걸이야?
What is this? Jewelry?
그가 선물이라며
He insisted on giving me
이 보석달린 귀걸이를 줬어요
this jewelry as a gift.
부탁해요
지금 여기서 말하고 있는걸 알면
Please.
He will kill me if he knows
그가 절 죽일거에요
that I was here talking to you.
당신은 이미 살인현장의
You're already in possession
도둑맞은 물건을 갖고있어요
of stolen property
from a murder scene.
탈옥범을 도와주고 있는건
Not to mention
말할 필요도 없구요
aiding and abetting a fugitive.
Memmo가 체포될 때, 저는 그와
함께 살고있었어요
I was living with Memmo
when they arrested him.
저도 조사받았구요
They investigated me, too.
그래서 전 제 딸의 양육권도 잃었어요
I lost custody of my daughter.
그래서 양육권을 되찾기 위해서는
Now, to have any chance
of ever getting her back,
안정적으로 사는 모습을
보여야 한댔어요
they said that I need
to show stability,
저 스스로 딸을 보살필 수
있을 정도로요
that I can support her
on my own.
이걸 팔 작정이었어요?
Were you going to sell this?
네 팔아서 저금하려구요
Yes, and put it into savings.
알겠죠? 전 그놈한테
선물같은거 원하지 않았어요
Okay? I-I didn't want
a gift from him.
원하지 않았다면 잘됐네요
Well, that will
work out nicely for you,
왜냐면 우리가 압수할거거든요
because we're keeping them.
당신 휴대폰도요
And the cell phone, too.
날 보세요
Look at me.
날 보라고!
Look at me!
Memmo가 당신에게 의지하는거 알고있어요
We know Memmo's leaning on you.
그 놈이 어디로 간다고 했어요?
Where did he say he was going?
말 안했어요
아무것도 말해주지 않았다구요
He didn't say.
He wouldn't tell me anything.
(Forest의사는 118번으로 연락바랍니다)
Dr. Forest, dial 118, please.
Dr Forest, please dial 1-1-8
Dr. Forest, please dial 1-1-8.
Dr Kravitz, you have a visitor
in the main lobby
Dr. Kravitz, you have a visitor
in the main lobby.
무슨일로 오셨어요?
Can I help you?
네, 질문할것이 있어서요
Yes, just a quick question.
당신이 여기서 일하기 시작한지
Do you happen to know,
by any chance,
얼마나 되었는지 알 수 있을까요?
when, uh, when you
started working here?
저요?
Me?
어 그러니까
Uh, let me see.
작년 8월부터 여기서 일해왔어요
I've been here since...
August of last year.
틀렸어
Wrong answer.
넌 여기 언제부터 일했어?
When did you start working here?
언제야!!
When?!
살려주세요! 1월이예요
Please! January!
틀렸어 너!
Wrong answer. You!
여기로 나와!
Step out, now!
당장!
Now!
언제부터 일했어?
When did you start
working here?
지난주요
Last week.
전 차량에게 알린다, 총기사건 발생
Attention all
units, gunshots exchanged,
데이드 병원에서 경관이 총에 맞았다
용의자는 무장했고 위험하다
officer down at Dade Memorial.
Suspect is armed and dangerous.
보안관
상황은 어떤가
Commander.
What have we got?
2명이 죽었습니다
We've got two dead,
1명 부상이구요
우린 빠졌습니다
one wounded.
We're in lockdown.
SWAT팀이 들어갔습니다
SWAT's on their way.
경찰견 데려오게 승강기 통로도
써야겠네
Take K-9. We'll use
the elevator shafts, too.
네
그 놈 아직도 여기 있는거 같아요
Okay.
He might still be here.
알아낼 방법이 하나 있지
There's one way to find out.
이봐 여기 트럭아래
Hey. There's some
버려진 옷이 있어요
discarded clothing
under the truck.
어때요? /Memmo가 버린 옷 같구만
What do you think? Does
it belong to Memmo?
옷 위에 방금 막 튄 액체자국이 있어
They've got fresh
spatter on them.
그가 여기서 출발했다면
It stands to reason,
if he departed from here,
이 트럭중 하나를 몰고갔다는 증거지
he used one of these trucks.
호라시오 반장이다
This is Lieutenant Caine.
탈옥범은 지금 9mm 권총을 가지고 있으며
The suspect is now in possession
9mm 권총을 가지고 있으며
of a department-issued
nine millimeter handgun
훔친 무전기를 가지고 있다
and has stolen a dispatch radio.
모든 무전기 사용시 주의하라
Please be careful
with all transmissions.
모든 차량에게 알린다
All units, all units.
CSI가 범인이 파란 죄수복을
버린것을 발견했다
CSI reports suspect Memmo Fierro
shed his blue coveralls
지금은 어떤 옷을 입고있는지 알 수 없다
and is now in unknown clothing.
무장하고 매우 위험한 범인이니
All units use caution,
모두 주의하라
as suspect should be considered
armed and extremely dangerous.
너 앞으로 나와! 빨리!
You! Step out! Now!
나와!
Step out!
왜 저는 살려줬을까요?
Why did he spare me?
아직 잘 모르겠습니다
We're not sure yet.
그는 계속해서 같은것을
He kept asking the same thing
물어봤어요
/ 그게 머였죠?
over and over.
What was that?
"여기 언제부터 일했어?"
"When did you
start working here?"
"여기 언제부터 일했어?"
"When did you start
working here?"
"여기 언제부터 일했어?"
"When did you
start working here?"
왜 그런거죠?
Why was he doing that?
이해가 안되요
It made no sense.
질문 하나 하죠
Let me ask you a question.
그가 어떤 특정 날짜를
말했었나요?
Did he mention any
specific calendar dates?
모르겠어요 아마도요
I don't know. Maybe.
저는 잠시 나갔다 올게요
I'm going to leave you
for a minute by yourself.
필요한거 있으면
저기있는 경관에게 말하면되요
This officer will bring you
anything you want. Okay?
많은 도움이 되었어요, 알겠죠?
You've been amazing, all right?
감사합니다
Thank you.
대체 무슨일이예요, 반장님
What the hell
is going on, Horatio?
병원 직원에게 총질을 해대고,
Guy opens fire on
a hospital staff,
다시 사라졌다구요?
then he's in the wind again?
뭐가 있을걸까, 월터군
What is he up to, Walter?
원하는게 뭘까?
What does he want?
갱들이 하는 복수극 같은걸지 몰라요
Could be avenging
some gang thing.
그럴수도 있지
/반장님?
I guess that's possible.
Lieutenant?
어? 반장님을 찾는 사람이 있습니다
Yeah? I got a civilian
requesting you.
우리 무전기 주파수로요
On our frequency.
호라시오입니다
This is Horatio Caine.
제 이름은 애런 테이버입니다
My name is Aaron Taber.
당신이 저를 체포하기 바래요
And I need for you to arrest me.
당신을 체포해달라구요?
무슨이유로요, 애런씨?
I need to arrest you?
For what reason, Aaron?
저는 제 일을 제대로 하지 않았어요
I didn't do my job.
무슨 일을 하시죠?
And what is that job?
전 죽고 싶지 않아요
I don't want to die.
죽고싶지 않다구요?
Memmo?
You don't want to die?
거기 있나?
Are you there?
끝나지 않은 일이 있어
Unfinished business,
호라시오 캐인
Horatio Caine.
그리고 오늘은 우울한 날이군
And this is my rainy day.
맞아, 그리고 내가 널 잡으면,
우울한 날은 마지막 날이 될거다, 메모야
Yes, and if I catch you,
it'll be your last, Memmo.
가슴아파하는 한 남자의 목소리가 기억나는군
I know the sound of a man
with a broken heart.
그게 한...
What's it been?
5년쯤 됐나?
Five years...
니가 니 신혼때 부인손을 잡아본지 말야
since you held your
newlywed wife's hand?
너를 꽉잡은채 말야
Still tugs at you.
Memmo야 그 일때문에
널 죽여버릴거다
Memmo... I'm going
to kill you for that.
내 말 기억해라
You mark my words.
월터군, 애런 테이버가 누군지
Walter, Aaron Taber.
찾아봐
Find him.
어떻게 생각해?
What do you think?
여기서 끝날거 같아?
You think it ends here?
널 용서했어
I forgive you...
니가 한 일 말야
for doing your job.
죽었네, 에릭
He's gone, Eric.
젠장!
Damn it.
왜 우리를 여기로 유인했을까?
Why would he lure us here?
그리고 이 남자에 대해 찾아낸거 있나?
And what do we know about him?
몰라요 월터가 조사중이예요
I don't know. Walter was
checking his background.
연락온 게 있나 확인해 볼게요
Let's see what he sent me.
그는 Find Us Families의 직원이구요
He was an employee at an agency
called Find Us Families.
사회복지사네요
A case worker.
아이를 입양시키는 일이군
Placing children.
Memmo가 감옥에 간 뒤에
After Memmo was in prison...
아동복지국이 와서 우리 집에 숨겨논
Child Services came and
found all of his guns
모든 총들을 찾아냈어요
still hidden away in my house.
전 숨겨놓지도 몰랐어요
I never knew.
알겠어요? 하지만 복지국에선
저를 믿지 않았아요
Okay? But they did
not believe me.
그때부터 저는 제 딸을 볼 수 있는
권리를 빼앗겼구요
And all visitation for Elsa was
restricted from that point on.
그리고,어,, 이 남자가
And, uh, this man was assigned
당신 딸 관련한 일을 담당한 사람인가요?
as the case worker
for your daughter?
네 그들이 우리 사건을
Yes. They
transferred
개인이 하는 회사로 보냈어요
our case to a-a
private company.
또 계속해서 통장잔고 이야기를 했어요
They kept talking about
a backlog or something.
그 남자는.. 당분간만 지낼만한 집을
He promised me
that he was going
제 딸을 위해 찾아주겠다고 약속했었어요
to find a good but
temporary home for Elsa.
Memmo가 오늘 그 사람을 총으로 죽였습니다
Memmo shot and killed him
in his own driveway today.
이유가 뭐죠?
Why would he do that?
Memmo는 이제 제 인생과 상관없는 사람이예요
Memmo's not in my life anymore.
그리고 저는 제 딸을 다시 볼 수만 있다면
And if I have any chance
of ever seeing Elsa again,
그 놈을 제 인생에 다시 들이지 않을거에요
I cannot let him
back in my life.
당신을 이미 다시 들여놨어요
You did just let him back in.
그리고 아무 말도 못해준다구요?
And you had no intention
of telling anyone.
제 자신을 보호하려는 것 뿐이에요
I was protecting myself.
이제 다른 사람을 보호할 차례에요, 이본씨
Maybe it is time to protect
someone else, Ivonne.
그놈은 그의 딸을 보고싶어 했어요,
He just wanted to
see his daughter,
전 안된다고 말했죠
and I told him
that he couldn't.
그랬더니 그가 저를 몰아세웠어요
And he pushed.
그 놈은 여러사람을 죽여대고 있어요
The man is on a killing spree.
왜 한번도 날 안 찾아왔어?
Why don't you
visit me, mi Amor?
날 봐, 딴눈 안파는게 좋을거야
Look at me. You better
not find someone else.
넌 항상 이런식으로 살거잖아
You can't be out like
this, okay, Memmo?
그냥 가줄래?
Just go, okay?
이본, 그냥 받아둬
Ivonne, just take it.
팔던지 갖던지 맘대로 해
Trade it, keep it, whatever.
우리 딸은 어딨어? 너랑 같이
여기 일하러 왔어?
Where's Elsa? Did she
come to work with you?
아니 걘 나랑 함께 못있어
No. She can't be with me,
이게 다 니가 한 짓 때문이야
because of everything
that you've done.
그들이 딸을 데려갔어
They took her!
무슨소리야? 누가 데려갔다는거야?
What are you talking
about? Who took her?
우리 딸은 입양됐어
She's in foster care.
한번도 감옥에 면회간적이 없어요
I never went to go
see him in prison.
그래서 복지사가 딸을 데려갔다는걸 설명했어요
So I had to explain that
a case worker had her.
이름이 애런이라는것도요 이 사람이요
A man named Aaron. Him.
Memmo는 오늘 데이드 병원에서
Memmo shot and killed
two intake workers
관련된 일꾼들 2명을 죽였어요
today at Dade Memorial.
애런 테이버가 그 병원과 어떤 관련이 있나요?
Aaron Taber have any
association with that hospital?
아니요
I don't think so.
몇 주 전에
A couple weeks ago,
딸 엘사가 급하게 병원에 갔었어요
Elsa was rushed
to the hospital.
애런이 말하길 일종의 사고가 있었다 그랬어요
And Aaron said there had been
some kind of accident
딸의 입양 가정에서요
in her new foster home.
전 그말을 듣고 너무 화가났어요
And it made me really angry.
메모한테 이 일을 말했나요?
You told Memmo
about this accident?
네 했어요!
Yes, I did!
그리고 전 모든 것이 그 놈 때문이라고 탓했어요
And I blamed him for everything.
그들이 엘사를 병원에 데려갔는데
They rushed her
to the hospital,
나는 그녀 근처에도 못가게 했어!
and they won't even
let me near her!
이게 다 니가 저지른 일 때문이야!
Because of what you did!
니가 우리 딸한테 피해를 준거라고!
You did this to her!
너 땜에 우리 딸이 고생하는거라고!
She's going through
this because of you!
그냥 그가 떠나는 거라고 생각했어요
I thought that he
was just going to leave.
무슨 짓을 또 꾸미는건지 전혀 몰랐어요
I never thought that he was
going to do anything, and...
죄송해요 저는 아무 말도 해드릴 수 없었어요
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have said anything.
이해해요, 이본씨
저는 그냥
I agree, Ivonne.
I just...
거기 앉아계세요 에릭?
Sit tight. Eric?
입양일을 하는 곳에 번호를 알아볼게요
I'll get on the phone with
the foster placement agency.
응, 좋은 생각이야
거기가 탈옥범의 다음 타겟이겠지
Yeah, that's a good idea.
It might be his next target.
네, 애런은 여기서 복지사로
Yeah, Aaron's been
거의 6년간 일했어요
a case worker here
almost six years.
모두가 충격먹었어요
Everyone's in shock.
저희는 탈옥수가 그 딸과 관련된
We're afraid this escapee
모든 사람을 타겟으로 정할까봐 걱정되요
is targeting everyone
associated with his daughter.
엘사 에르난데스?
불쌍한 것
Elsa Hernandez?
Poor girl.
메모 피에로 같은 아빠 아래 태어나다니
Born into this world
with Memmo Fierro as her father.
그래서 이 사건을 잘 알고 계신가요?
So you're familiar
with the case?
지금 엘사는 어디있는지 아세요?
Do you know where she is now?
어, 아니요, 사실 그 일은
전부 애런이 했거든요
Uh, no, actually,
that was all Aaron.
시에서 하는 아이 입양서비스를 우린
We're faster than
the city services
훨씬 더 빨리 처리해요, 하지만 직원들끼리
at placing children
with families, but we don't
하는 일을 공유할 시간은 별로 없죠그래서...
have a lot of time to compare
notes with each other, so...
애런 책상에서
Let me pull the file
파일을 한번 찾아보죠
Kenneth?
from Aaron's desk.
러셀한테 전화왔어요
I have Russell on one.
잠깐 기다리라고해
Hold the calls, please.
네, 네
Yes, yes,
그 딸은 지금
his daughter is
currently living
새엄마와 함께 살고있네요
감사하빈다
with a foster mom.
Thank you.
실례합니다만, 봐도 될까요?
Excuse me.
May I see that?
음, 나 월턴데,
Thanks. Um...
Hey, H. Yeah, it's Walter.
딸은 지금 입양되서
새엄마랑 살고있데
So, uh, the daughter
is living with a foster mom...
이름은 조엔 코너스,
가드니아가 312번지에 살아
a woman named Joanne Connors...
at 312 Gardenia Drive.
Ok
Okay.
찾으면 알려줄게
I'll let you know
what we find out.
지금 그쪽으로 출발했어
They're headed
over right now. Okay.
그러니까 애런이 생물학적 엄마에게
So, I understand
that Aaron had told
딸이 병원에 갔다고 말을 해줬다구요
the biological mother that there'd
been some sort of a hospital visit?
네네, 그날 기억나요
Oh, yes, yes,
I remember that day.
네 그는 오후 내내 새엄마를 도우러
Uh, yeah, he was gone
most of the afternoon
가있었어요...
집안에서 난 사고로 보였어요
assisting the foster mom... a
household accident, apparently.
딸애는 팔에 2도화상을 입었고,
The girl had second-degree
burns on her arm and was admitted
파일로비스타 의료센터로 갔어요
to Palo Vista Medical Center.
데이드 병원이 아니구요 아마 그쪽은
환자를 바로 받을수 없었나봐요
Not Dade Memorial. Probably 'cause
they couldn't take her right away.
엄마, 나 아파
Mommy, it hurts.
제발요, 딸애가 너무 아파해요
Please, she's in a lot of pain
지금 해주세요
right now.
사정은 알겠지만, 지금 너무 많은
I understand, but we have
응급환자들이 있어요
a lot of emergencies, sir.
저기 앉아 기다리시던지,
파일로 비스타병원으로 데려가세요
Take a seat over there,
or take her to Palo Vista.
40km는 더 떨어져 있는곳이잖아요
That's, like, ten miles away.
선택권이 없네요 죄송해요
Those are the choices.
We're sorry.
Mendez!
고마워요
Thank you.
잠시 기다려주실래요?
Can you give us a minute?
네 물론이죠
Yeah, sure.
그래서 메모가 그런 질문들을 해댄거였어
That's why Memmo showed up
there asking those questions.
딸을 돌아가게한 사람들에게
책임을 물을거였어
He was trying to get the people
responsible for turning her away.
어, 여기서 일한지 얼마나
Uh, do you know, uh,
됐는지 알 수 있을까요?
by any chance when
you started working here?
작년 8월부터요
I've been here since
August of last year.
정답이 아니군
Wrong answer.
그런 논리로 생각해본다면
And if you follow that logic,
딸은 새엄마랑 있을때
화상을 입고 아파했어
she suffered the burn injury
on the foster mom's watch.
새엄마도 죽이러 가겠네
She could be a target, too.
세상에
Oh, God.
아무도 없어요, 반장님
It's clear, H.
울프군, 구급차 부르게
Mr. Wolfe, call an ambulance.
CSI 울프다
가드니아 거리 312번지로
This is CSI Wolfe.
I need an R.A. unit at 312
구급차 요청한다!당장!
/휴대폰을 여기에 뒀어요
Gardenia Drive! Now!
I left my phone out here.
Here we go
Here we go.
그 사람은 대머리에
He was bald...
문신을 했어요
and wore tattoos.
네, 가만히 계세요
Okay, nice and easy.
다리를 들어올리겠습니다
We're gonna elevate this leg.
많이 아프신거 알아요
I know you're in a lot of pain.
엘사는 어딨죠?
/ 몰라요
Where is Elsa?
I don't know!
총쏜사람이 딸을
Did the man
데려갔나요?
who shot you take the girl?
그 놈이 데려갔어요?
Did he take the girl?
아뇨
No.
그 놈에게 딸은 이미 집을 나갔다 그랬어요
No, I told him she
was gone already.
학교에 갔다가
집에 안들어왔거든요
She went to school,
and she didn't come home.
딸을 이틀 꼬박 찾았어요
I've spent
the past two days trying to find her.
이틀이요?
이틀이나 실종됬어요?
Two days?
She's been missing for two days,
그리고 신고도 안했어요?
you haven't reported her?
지금 장난해요?
Are you kidding me?
부인 가만히 계세요
Ma'am, hang in there...
호라시오, 내 딸 어딨어?
Horatio, where is she?
내 딸 어딨냐고
Where's my daughter?
나도 몰라,
하지만 찾을거야
I don't have her,
but I'm gonna find her.
내가 왜 널 믿어야 되는데?
나도 못찾아내는 주제에
Why am I supposed to believe you?
You can't even find me.
그건 니가 도망치고 있으니까 그런거고
That's because you're
running from me.
딸이 안도망치고 있다는건
어떻게 아는데?
How do you know she's
not running, Horatio?
지금 혼자서 무서워 하고 있는지 없는지
어떻게 아냐고
How do you know she's not somewhere
right now, alone and afraid?
그게 우리 일이니까 넌 자수나 해
우린 딸에 집중하게
Here's what we do... you turn
yourself in, we focus on Elsa.
이 도시는 딸이 안좋은 일을
겪기 시작한 곳이야
This is the city that let her fall
through the cracks to begin with.
시에서 우리 딸을 엄마한테서 뺏어갔다고
They took Elsa from her mother.
그 엄마는 냉혹한 살인마랑 살고 있었잖나
Her mother was living with
a cold-blooded killer, Memmo.
그들이 내 딸을 아무렇게나
그들 시스템에 내던져놓고 방치했어
They dumped my little girl into the
system and they forgot about her.
왜 그런 한심한 새엄마한테 남겨두냐고
Why else would they leave her
with a pathetic woman?
그놈들은 신경도 안써
서류상으로 처리만하면 관심 끄자나
They don't care... it's all
about their damn spreadsheets.
그 서류들 다 없애버릴거고
I'm gonna take
those spreadsheets
그 서류와 관련된 사람들
모두를 죽여버리겠어
and I'm gonna
hang them with them.
그리고 넌 내딸을 찾아서
내앞에 보이지 않으면
And if you don't show me
my little girl,
일은 더 나빠질거야
all of this is gonna get
a lot worse.
알아들어?
Do you understand me?
완전 피범벅이네
Whoa. That's
a lot of blood.
그여잔 괜찮데?
응 우리가 제때 도착했어
She gonna be all right?
Yeah, we got to her in time,
하지만 딸은 아직도 실종상태야
but the little girl's
still missing.
글고 트립이 말하길 딸을 마지막으로 본게
And Tripp says the last time
she was seen was boarding a bus
금요일에 스쿨버스 탈때래
at the end of
the school day on Friday.
그러니까 그는 버스경로는 파악했을거야
So he's canvassing
the bus route,
그가 나타날만한 학교 지리를
생각했겠지
he's canvassing
the campus to see
그러면 딸이 이 집으로 다시 안오는거면
what he can turn up.
So what should we
여기서 멀 찾아봐야 하는거야?
be looking for, if
she never came home?
응, 그게말이야
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
새엄마가 아무한테도
실종된 사실을 말하지 않았어
The foster mother never
told anyone she was missing.
무언가를 숨기고 있는거야
She's covering for something.
맞아
/맞아, 그 여자는 확실히
Yeah.
Yeah, she's definitely
숨기는 게 있어...
그리고 내가 내기하는데
covering something up...
and I bet you
그건 이 집안과 관련된거야
it's right here in this house.
딸애 침실은 어디야?
Where's the girl's bedroom?
이쪽이야
Bedroom's this way.
난 밖을 조사할게
I'll go to work outside.
자, 이쪽면이 뜯겨졌고
All right, so the screen's
been busted out,
창문 틀에 지렛대로 연
흔적이 있네
and I got pry marks along the
bottom edge of the window frame.
창문 틀이 파손됐네
Window frame's split.
누군가가 침입하려 한거 같은데
Looks like someone
tried to jam it open.
응, 바로 여기
누군가가 침입을 시도했어
Yeah, right here.
Somebody was trying
딸애 침실로 들어오려고 말야
to break in
to this little girl's room.
칩입자가 증거를 남겨놨길 기도하자구
Let's hope that the intruder
left some evidence behind.
머 얻은거 있어?
넌 뭐 찾은거 있어?
What do you got?
You got something?
찢어진 종지조각이 있어
Got a torn piece of paper
머가 써있는데
with some printing on it.
이봐 난 아무것도 없어
All right, guys, I got nothing
하지만 이 작은 종이조각은 있네
but this little piece of paper
that doesn't belong.
종이를 찾았어?
You got a piece of paper?
에릭아 너도 종이조각
찾았다 그랬지?
Eric, you got
a piece of paper, too?
알면서 멀물어
You know I do.
그러면 아마 둘이 연관성이 있을지도
So maybe they're connected.
어이, 니 종이조각이랑 내거랑
Hey, so your
piece of paper and mine
확실히 같은 곳에서 나온거야
are definitely
from the same source.
질감과 두께가 동일해
Identical texture
and thickness.
이 조각에 이부분 말야
This piece right here,
접힌 자국이 있어
it has a crease...
짜잔, 여기말야
bang, right there.
내생각엔 자르고 나누려고
So I'm thinking maybe
it was folded over something
여러번 접은 종이같아
/맞아, 내말은
before ripping and separating.
Yeah, I mean,
블록체로 써진 마지막 글씨부분같아
that's the last
of the block lettering.
응, 저 줄무늬는
Yeah, that stripe...
전문가용 프린터로 인쇄된거야
It's professional printing.
사업상 보낸 편지 같은거야
It looks like it's from a
local business or something.
우리 지금 잘되가고 있는거지?
We're grasping, huh?
그렇긴 하지
Yeah.
근데 저건 전단지나, 피자 광고지나
It could be from a flyer,
a pizza joint...
슈퍼마켓 행사광고나 머든지 될 수 있어
junk mail from a retail store...
그거 아러?
You know what?
이근처 사업하는 매장 목록이 있어
Here's a list of all the
businesses in the area.
이건가?
/아니,내 생각엔
This one?
No, I think
글씨체가 너무 두꺼워
the lettering is too bold.
색깔도 다르고
The color is off on that one.
Hey
Hey.
찾았다!
Bingo!
황금태양세탁소
Golden Sun Dry Cleaners.
좋아! 자 이제 우린 새엄마가 새탁하는 곳을 알아냈구만
Great! Now we know where the
foster mom does her laundry,
하지만 이건 딸을 찾는데 도움이 안되
but it won't help us
locate the missing girl.
아니,아니,
새엄마가 아니라 생물학적 엄마를 생각해봐
No. No, you're thinking
of the wrong mom.
엘사의 진짜엄마
Elsa's mom,
이본 에르난데스,
그 여자 세탁소에서 일한댔어
Ivonne Hernandez,
she works at a dry cleaners.
그녀는 저 세탁소 직원이야
She works at that dry cleaners.
에르난데스씨, 그 집에 갔어요, 안갔어요?
Were you or were you not in
the house, Ms. Hernandez?
질문에 답변 하세요
Just answer the question.
갔었어요, 됐어요?
I was, okay?
갔었다구요
I was.
하지만 그건 메모가 탈옥하기
But it was a couple weeks ago,
2주 전이었다구요
before Memmo had gotten out.
엘사와 새엄마 둘다
집에 있지도 않았다구요
Elsa and the foster mom,
they weren't even home.
거기서 뭐했어요?
What were you doing there?
몰라요
I don't know.
애런이 제가 딸을 방문할 수 있게 해줬어요
Aaron had got me
some visits with her,
하지만 그걸론 충분하지 않았어요
but it wasn't enough.
딸애가 자해를 한다고 말해줘서
He had told me that
she had hurt herself,
걱정이 됐어요
and I worried.
어떻게는 저는 딸 근처에
가고 싶었어요
I needed to be near her somehow.
거기 잠깐 있었는데,
정말 맘이 편해졌어요
For a minute there,
it made me feel better.
제가 실수한거 알아요, 하지만
I know I've made
mistakes, but...
당신들이 제 딸을 찾으러 가게 해주세요
you've got to let
me go find her.
우린 못해요
We can't.
당신을 보호하기 위해, 여기 잡아놔야 해요
In order to keep you safe,
we need to keep you here.
괜찮아요
She's right.
우리가 딸을 찾을게요
All right?
Let us find her.
그 놈이 먼저 찾기전에
You find her...
당신이 먼저 딸애 찾아내요
before he does.
그럴게요, 약속합니다
We will. I promise.
무슨생각해?
What are you thinking?
우리가 한 약속을
지킬수 있게되길 바래
Yeah, I'm thinking I hope
that's a promise we can keep.
새엄마와 다리 총알에 대한
I ran a report
보고서 읽었어
on the foster mother with
a bullet hole in her leg.
알아보니 2년전에 그 여자와 살던
Turns out she had
입양된 9살 짜리 소년이 있었어
a nine-year-old under her care
two years ago,
그 아이도 병원 치료를 받았었고
and he was hospitalized.
저거봐
내가 뭐가 궁금한줄 알아?
Look at that.
You know what I'd like to know?
어떻게 이런 여자가 엘사를
I'd like to know
how this foster mom
맡을 자격이 됐는지 궁금하다
/ 모르지
even qualified to take care of Elsa.
I don't know.
Find Us Families회사의 모든 일처리과정이 수상해
The whole Find Us Families
operation is hinky.
이 회사 직원명단 조사해볼래?
Will you look through
the employee roster?
엘사가 어디갔는지 알만한 사람이
There's got to be at
least one person
적어도 한명은 있을거야
/알았어
who has an idea of where
the girl is. Yeah.
Find Us Families.
How may I help you?
네네 좋아요, 고마워요
Okay, great.
Thanks.
Find Us Families社입니다
무슨일이신가요?
Find Us
Families. How may I help you?
뭐 건졌어?
/아니
Anything?
No.
아니, 경관들이 아직도 집집마다
No, patrol's still
just going door to door
딸애 친구들 방문해서 묻고있어
talking to all
of her school friends.
넌 뭐 찾았어?
Did you find anything,
파일에 갈만한데 안써있어?
any prior placement
location in her file?
우리가 이미 아는곳 말곤 없어
Nothing that we didn't
know already.
Kenneth McGuire은 이 회사 대표야
Well, Kenneth McGuire
is the agency rep here.
월터랑 내가 이미 이야기해 봤는데
Walter and I spoke to
him earlier.
그는 직원명단을 우리에게 주기로 했었어
He was supposed to give us
his employee roster.
비서가 곧 돌아올거라고 그랬어
Secretary says he'll
be back in a minute.
애런 테이버는 그 집에 정기적으로 방문했어
Aaron Taber made
regular visits to the house.
그것뿐만 아니야 이거 봐봐
He did more than
that; look at this.
옳은 일을 하려고 노력했다고 써있네
Says here he was trying to do
the right thing;
애런이 엘사를 다른집으로 보내는것을 제안했네
He recommended that Elsa be
removed from her foster home.
조엔 코너스가 새엄마로 일하는 것을
He recommends
that Joanne Connors
끝내야 한다고 제안했어
be terminated
as a foster mother.
그런데 이 모든것은 거부되써
But the whole thing is denied.
누가 거부한거야?
Kenneth McGuire
By who?
Kenneth McGuire.
Kenneth McGuire는 엘사와 관련된 일에 대해
Kenneth McGuire said
he didn't know anything
자기는 아무것도 모른다 그랬는데
/ 그래, 너한테 거짓말 한거야
about Elsa Hernandez's case.
Yeah, he was lying to you.
그는 다 알고 있었어
He knew it inside and out.
조엔 코너스 음성사서함입니다
You have reached
the voicemail of Joanne Connors.
메세지를 남겨주세요, 제가 다시 연락...
Please leave a message,
and I'll get back...
이건 조엔 코너스 번호야
It just connected me
to Joanne Connors.
그러면 맥과이어는 엘사의 새엄마와
직접 연락을 하고있었던거네
So, McGuire has a direct line
to Elsa's foster mom.
이 사람은 대체 어디간거야?
Where the hell is this guy?
저기요
Hey, excuse me?
지금 이 회사는 경찰 조사
You do know that this agency
받고 계신거 아시죠?
is under police
investigation, right?
지금 당장 맥과이어씨와 대화해야겠어요!
I need to speak to
McGuire right now!
5분후에 말구요 지금 당장이요
Not five minutes
from now. Now!
대표님은 10분전에 도착하셨어야 하는데
He was supposed to be
back ten minutes ago.
저도 어디계신지 몰라요
I don't know where he is.
전화해봐요, 지금 당장 전화하는게 좋을겁니다
You call him. You need to make
that phone call right now.
지금 당장
/해봤는데 받지 않으세요
Right now.
I tried. He's not answering.
다시 해봐요
Let's call him again.
너땜에 행복하다 엘사야
I'm happy for you, Elsa.
착한 아이에겐 좋은 일이 생기지
Good things happen
to good kids.
이런 가족과 함께라면,
예전은 다 잊어버릴걸
A family like this, you'll
never have to look back.
대표님 차번호는 몰라요
I don't know his license plate.
어떤 차종인지는 아세요?
Do you know what kind
of car he drives?
렉서스예요
Some kind of Lexus.
색깔이랑 모델은요?
내가 정보요청하고있어
A color? A model?
I'm getting that information.
차에 GPS기기 달려있어요?
네비게이션 달려있어요?
Does the car have a GPS unit?
Does it have navigation?
네,네
Ok
Yeah, yes.
Okay.
네비 달려있데
The car has navigation.
호라시오인데,
This is Lieutenant Caine.
지금 유괴 용의자 추적중이다
We are tracking a possible
kidnapping suspect.
알겠습니다 반장님
Copy that, Lieutenant.
레져베이션 공원길 근처
Assistance requested for all
units in the vicinity
모든 차량을에게 요청한다
of Reservation Parkway.
반복한다, Reservation Parkway다
Repeat, Reservation Parkway.
시동 꺼!
Kill the engine!
Let's go!
시동 끄고, 차키 밖으로 던져! 당장!
Kill the engine and toss
those keys, right now!
빨리!
Do it!
손 높이 올려!
두손 보이게 올려!
Hands up high!
Let me see those hands.
그래, 천천히
Okay, slowly...
밖으로 나와
get out of the vehicle.
내가 손 볼수있게 하고
Hands where I can see them.
아주 좋아, Kenneth군
Very good, Kenneth.
그러니까...
여기서 뭐하고 있는건가?
So... what are
you doing out here?
저 아이가 누릴만한 인생을 마련해주려고...
I'm
giving her the life she deserves,
그동안 겪을 일들을 잊을수 있게요
after everything
she's been through.
봐요, 저 집들은 부유한 집안에
Look, beyond those gates
is a wealthy family
저 아이를 보살피고 사랑해 줄거라구요
that will love her
and take care of her.
그 사랑에 니가 받는 수수료는 얼만데?
And what is your cut
of that love, Kenneth?
그게 내생각이다
That's what I thought.
생물학적 엄마는 생각 안해봤나?
What about the biological mom?
그 살인마 마누라 말야?
그래
A death row inmate's
girlfriend? Yeah...
너조차도 믿지 않았던 그 여자 말하는거냐
Even you don't believe that.
날 믿어, 아무도 저 아이를 찾지 않을거야
Believe me. No one was going
looking for this girl.
- 니가 틀렸어, Kenneth
- 반장님!
- You're wrong, Kenneth.
- H.
핸들에 손 올리고
차 안에 있어
Keep your hands on the steering
wheel and stay in the car!
실력 좋네, 반장
날 실망시키지 않을 줄 알았어
You're good, Horatio.
I knew you wouldn't let me down.
그를 보내줘, Memmo
Let him go, Memmo.
한방에 맞출 수 있어요, 반장님
/ 진정하게, 에릭
I got a clean shot, H.
Easy, Eric.
넌 너무 착해서
내딸앞에서 날 못죽여
You're too good a man to kill me
in front of my own daughter.
가족이 얼마나 중요한건지 넌 알지?
You know how important
family is, don't you?!
닥쳐 나한테 가족 이야기
하지마라
You shut your mouth. You don't
talk to me about family.
내 딸 밖으로 나오라그래
얼굴 좀 보게
Bring her out.
I want to see her now.
그건 안되지
/ 데려오라고!!
Not a chance.
Bring her out!
아니면 바로 이 놈
머리 날라간다
Or I put one in this
gavacho's head, man.
엘사야 잘들어,
당장 차 안으로 돌아가라
Elsa, listen to me, go
back to the car right now.
당장!
Right now!
안녕, 애기야
나 기억하니?
Hi, sweetie.
Do you remember me?
많이 컷구나
You're getting so big.
정말 다컷네 이제...
Memmo...
You're all grown up.
그를 놓아줘
/ 엘사야, 잘들어
let him go. Elsa, listen to me.
This is probably
이제 난 떠나니까
이게 아마 나를 볼 마지막일거 같아
the last time you're going to
see me, 'cause I have to leave.
모든일이 이제 잘 될거야
Everything's going to be
okay now, though.
날 위해서 착하게 커야한다
Just be good for me.
엘사야?
Elsa?
지금 빨리 차로 돌아가라
/그럴 수 있지?
Go back to the car right now.
Can you do that?
내가 있어야 할 곳이 있지
I've got somewhere to be.
내 뒤를 쫓는가면, 이놈은 죽는다
If I even smell a cop tailing me...
Memmo야
/ 제가 맞출 수 있어요!
he's done. Memmo?
I'm gonna take him!
진정해,에릭 /메모!
/반장님, 쏠수 있다구요!
Easy, Eric. Memmo!
H, I'm gonna take him!
쏘지 말아요
Please don't shoot him.
제발요
엘사야...
Please.
Elsa, baby...
사랑한다
I love you.
미안하다
I'm sorry.
메모야, 오늘은 이 아이를 찾은 날이지만
Memmo, today is about her.
다음엔 널 찾을거다
Tomorrow will be about you.
괜찮니?
You okay?
CSI 델코입니다
지원 요청합니다
This is CSI Delko.
Please be advised... All right.
도난당한 노란 택시가
오크 힐 동쪽으로 가고있습니다
We have a stolen yellow cab
heading East on Oak Hill.
Ok
운전자는 메모 피에로입니다
Okay.
Passenger is Memmo Fierro.
총을 갖고있습니다
He is armed with a hostage.
반복한다 총을 갖고있다
I repeat... he has a hostage.
가보세요
Go ahead.
세상에
Oh, my God.
이제 모든게 괜찮을거다, 우리 딸
Everything's gonna be
okay, baby, okay?
엄마가 절 더이상 사랑하지 않는다고 생각했어요
I thought you didn't
love me anymore.
아니야
No.
다시는 그런 생각 마
Don't you ever think that.
언제나 널 사랑한단다
I will always love you.
여러분
Ladies...
행운을 빌어요
Good luck.
제작자 : 니코틴워터 (부족하지만 좋게 봐주세요~)
수정요청 : DC CSI갤러리 게시판에 '니코틴워터'를 제목에 넣어서
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com